Sculpture Photograph Collection: Italy-United States
Yale University Arts Library
- United States (Box 238)
  - Known Artists., 1743 (Box 239)
    - D, 91 (Box 243)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 23 (Box 243)
        - Drury, Alfred, 1856-1944., 1 (Box 243)
        - Duble, Lu, 1896-1970., 1 (Box 243)
        - Duff, John, XX C., 2 (Box 243)
        - Durham, Jimmie, XX C., 1 (Box 243)
        - Dykaar, Moses, -1933., 1 (Box 243)
      - Individual Artists., 68 (Box 243)
        - Dallin, Cyrus E., 1861-1944., 11 (Box 243)
        - Davidson, Jo, 1883-1952., 30 (Box 244)
        - Davis, Emma Lu, 1905-., 4 (Box 244)
        - Davis, Richard, 1904-., 3 (Box 244)
        - Dine, James, 1935-., 2 (Box 244)
        - Di Suvero, Mark, 1933-., 16 (Box 244)
        - Duveneck, Frank, 1848-1919., 2 (Box 244)
    - E, 28 (Box 244)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 4 (Box 244)
        - Eldred, Dale, 1933-., 1 (Box 244)
        - Ellerhusen, Ulric Henry, 1879-., 1 (Box 244)
        - Elozua, Raymon, 1947-., 1 (Box 244)
        - Esherick, Wharton, 1887-., 1 (Box 244)
      - Individual Artists., 24 (Box 244)
        - Eakins, Thomas, 1844-1916., 18 (Box 244)
        - Edstrom, David, 1873-., 6 (Box 244)
    - F, 108 (Box 245)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 19 (Box 245)
        - Feigenbaum, Harriet, 1939-., 1 (Box 245)
        - Ferrara, Jackie, 1929-., 2 (Box 245)
        - Fine, Jud, 1944-., 1 (Box 245)
        - Flanagan, John F., 1865-1952., 2 (Box 245)
        - Flavin, Dan, 1933-., 2 (Box 245)
        - Fleischner, Richard, 1944-., 3 (Box 245)
        - Foster, Robert, XX C., 1 (Box 245)
        - Frank, Mary, 1933-., 3 (Box 245)
        - Frazier, Paul, 1922-., 1 (Box 245)
        - Fredericks, Marshall, 1908-., 1 (Box 245)
        - Frisch, Victor, 1876-., 1 (Box 245)
        - Fuller, Sue, 1914-., 1 (Box 245)
      - Individual Artists., 89 (Box 245)
        - Falkenstein, Claire, 1908-., 3 (Box 245)
        - Ferber, Herbert, 1906-., 26 (Box 245)
        - Flannagan, John B., 1898-1942., 22 (Box 245)
        - Fraser, James Earle, 1876-1953., 4 (Box 246)
        - Fraser, Laura Gardin, 1889-., 4 (Box 246)
        - Frazee, John, 1790-1852., 3 (Box 246)
        - French, Daniel Chester, 1850-1931., 18 (Box 246)
        - Friedlander, Leo, 1889-1966., 5 (Box 246)
          See also: Architecture, U.S., XX C., 1933 Century of Progress, Hall of Social Science.
        - Frishmuth, Harriet, XX C., 4 (Box 246)
    - G, 49 (Box 247)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 18 (Box 247)
        - Gallo, Frank, 1933-., 1 (Box 247)
        - Garrison, Robert, 1896-., 1 (Box 247)
        - Ginnever, Charles, 1931-., 1 (Box 247)
        - Ginz, Walter, XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 247)
        - Gober, Robert, 1954-., 2 (Box 247)
        - Goldsmith, David, 1901-1980., 1 (Box 247)
        - Goler, Victor, XX C., 1 (Box 247)
        - Goodnough, Robert, 1917-., 1 (Box 247)
        - Gottlieb, Adolph, 1903-1974., 1 (Box 247)
        - Gould, Thomas, 1818-1881., 1 (Box 247)
        - Graham, Cecilia, XX C., 1 (Box 247)
        - Graham, Robert, 1938-., 1 (Box 247)
        - Greene, George S., XX C., 1 (Box 247)
        - Grippe, Peter, XX C., 1 (Box 247)
        - Grooms, Red, 1937-., 2 (Box 247)
        - Grosvenor, Robert, 1937-., 1 (Box 247)
        - Gudbrod, Louis, 1872-., 1 (Box 247)
        - Guinzburg, Frederick, 1897-., 1 (Box 247)
      - Individual Artists., 31 (Box 247)
        - Grafly, Charles, 1862-1925., 4 (Box 247)
        - Graves, Nancy, 1940-., 6 (Box 247)
        - Greenough, Horatio, 1805-1852., 8 (Box 247)
        - Gregory, John, 1879-1958., 7 (Box 247)
        - Gregory, Waylande, 1905-., 2 (Box 247)
        - Gross, Chaim, 1904-., 4 (Box 247)
    - H, 74 (Box 248)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 34 (Box 248)
        - Hadzi, Dimitri, 1921-., 2 (Box 248)
        - Hafner, Charles Andrew, 1888-., 1 (Box 248)
        - Hague, Raoul, 1905-., 3 (Box 248)
        - Hammond, Harmony, 1942-., 1 (Box 248)
        - Hammons, David, 1943-., 1 (Box 248)
        - Harkavy, Minna, 1895-., 1 (Box 248)
        - Harris, Paul, 1925-., 2 (Box 248)
        - Hawkins, Benjamin, 1896-., 1 (Box 248)
        - Hayes, David V., 1931-., 3 (Box 248)
        - Hesketh, XX C., 2 (Box 248)
        - Hinman, Charles, 1932-., 2 (Box 248)
        - Hokanson, Hans, 1925-., 2 (Box 248)
        - Horn, Roni, 1955-., 1 (Box 248)
        - Houser, Allan, 1914-., 1 (Box 248)
        - Hsu, Tishan, 1951-., 1 (Box 248)
        - Hughes, Robert Ball, 1806-1868., 1 (Box 248)
        - Hughes, Toni, XX C., 3 (Box 248)
        - Huneker, XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 248)
        - Hunt, Bryan, 1947-., 4 (Box 248)
        - Hunt, William Morris, 1824-1879., 1 (Box 248)
      - Individual Artists., 40 (Box 248)
        - Hall, George W., XX C. (Box 248)
        - Hanson, Duane, 1925-1996., 10 (Box 248)
        - Hare, David, 1917-., 6 (Box 248)
        - Heizer, Michael, 1944-., 9 (Box 248)
        - Hering, Henry, XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 248)
        - Hoffman, Malvina, 1887-1966., 6 (Box 248)
        - Hosmer, Harriet, 1830-1908., 3 (Box 248)
        - Huntington, Anna Hyatt, 1876-1973., 5 (Box 248)
    - I, 10 (Box 249)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 10 (Box 249)
        - Indiana, Robert, 1928-., 1 (Box 249)
        - Insley, Will, 1929-., 3 (Box 249)
        - Irwin, Robert, 1928-., 3 (Box 249)
        - Israel, Margaret, 1929-., 1 (Box 249)
        - Ives, Chauncy B., 1810-1894., 2 (Box 249)
    - J, 25 (Box 249)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 8 (Box 249)
        - Jaegers, Albert, XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 249)
        - Jenney, Neil, 1945-., 1 (Box 249)
        - Jimenez, Luis, 1940-., 2 (Box 249)
        - Johns, Jasper, 1930-., 3 (Box 249)
        - Jones, Th. Hudson, XX C., 1 (Box 249)
      - Individual Artists., 17 (Box 249)
        - Jennewein, C. Paul, 1890-., 10 (Box 249)
        - Judd, Donald, 1928-1997(?)., 7 (Box 249)
    - K, 66 (Box 249)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 22 (Box 249)
        - Kahler, Herman, ?., 1 (Box 249)
        - Kauffman, Craig, 1932-., 2 (Box 249)
        - Kendrick, Mel, 1949-., 1 (Box 249)
        - Kent, Adaline, XX C., 1 (Box 249)
        - Kienholz, Edward, 1927-, and Nancy., 3 (Box 249)
        - Kiestler, Frederick, XX C., 1 (Box 249)
        - King, William, 1925-., 3 (Box 249)
        - Kipp, Lyman, 1929-., 2 (Box 249)
        - Kitson, Henry Hudson, 1863/65-1947., 1 (Box 249)
        - Kohn, Gabriel, 1910-., 1 (Box 249)
        - Kottler, Howard, 1930-1989., 2 (Box 249)
        - Kramer, Reuben, 1909-., 1 (Box 249)
        - Kratina, George, XX C., 1 (Box 249)
        - Kruger, Louise, XX C., 1 (Box 249)
      - Individual Artists., 44 (Box 249)
        - Kalish, Max, 1891-., 5 (Box 250)
        - Keck, Charles, 1875-1951., 5 (Box 250)
        - Kiesler, Frederick, 1896-., 8 (Box 250)
        - Kirchmayer, John, 1850-1930., 2 (Box 250)
        - Konti, Isidore, 1862-1938., 3 (Box 250)
        - Koons, Jeff, 1953-., 4 (Box 250)
        - Korbel, Mario, 1882-1954., 12 (Box 250)
        - Kraus, Romauld, 1891-1954., 3 (Box 250)
        - Kreis, Henry, 1899-., 2 (Box 250)
    - L, 166 (Box 251)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 17 (Box 251)
        - Lamson, Joseph, XVIII C., 1 (Box 251)
        - Lantz, M., XX C., 1 (Box 251)
        - Lekakis, Michael, 1907-., 1 (Box 251)
        - Lentelli, Leo, 1879-1961., 1 (Box 251)
        - Levine, Les, 1936-., 2 (Box 251)
        - Lewis, Edmonia, 1845-c.1900., 3 (Box 251)
        - Linder, Jean, XX C., 1 (Box 251)
        - Loeb, Sidney, XX C., 1 (Box 251)
        - Lonas, Jo Henry, 1925-., 1 (Box 251)
        - Lucero, Michael, 1953-., 2 (Box 251)
        - Luna, James, XX C., 1 (Box 251)
        - Lye, Len, 1901-1980., 2 (Box 251)
      - Individual Artists., 149 (Box 251)
        - Lachaise, Gaston, 1882-1935., 27 (Box 251)
        - Lassow, Ibram, 1913-., 11 (Box 251)
        - Laurent, Robert, 1890-1970., 24 (Box 251)
        - Lawrie, Lee, 1877-1963., 32 (Box 252)
        - Lee, Arthur, 1881-1961., 3 (Box 252)
        - LeWitt, Sol, 1928-., 5 (Box 252)
        - Liberman, Alexander, 1912-., 13 (Box 252)
        - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1923-., 5 (Box 252)
        - Lippold, Richard, 1915-., 8 (Box 252)
        - Lipton, Seymour, 1903-., 11 (Box 252)
        - Lovet-Lorski, Boris, 1891-., 5 (Box 253)
        - Lukeman, Augustus, 1871-1935., 3 (Box 253)
        - Lux, Gwen, active from 1933., 2 (Box 253)
    - M, 145 (Box 253)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 27 (Box 253)
        - MacDonald, L., XIX C.(?)., 1 (Box 253)
        - Mallary, Robert, 1917-., 2 (Box 253)
        - Manley, Edna, 1900-., 1 (Box 253)
        - Margoulies, Berta, XX C., 1 (Box 253)
        - Maria Bergler, Ettore de, 1851-., 1 (Box 253)
        - Martiny, Philip, 1858-., 1 (Box 253)
        - Matta-Clark, Gordon, 1945-1978., 1 (Box 253)
        - Mayer, Rosemary, 1943-., 1 (Box 253)
        - McCollum, Allan, 1944-., 1 (Box 253)
        - Mead, L. G., XIX C., 1 (Box 253)
        - Mikus, Elenore, 1927-., 1 (Box 253)
        - Morahan, Eugene, 1869-., 1 (Box 253)
        - Morris, George L. K., XX C., 1 (Box 253)
        - Morris, Robert, 1931-., 3 (Box 253)
        - Morse, Samuel F. B., 1791-1872., 1 (Box 253)
        - Motto, Joseph C., 1892-., 2 (Box 253)
        - Mozier, Joseph, 1812-1870., 2 (Box 253)
        - Murray, Robert, 1936-., 1 (Box 253)
        - Murray, Samuel, 1870-., 3 (Box 253)
        - Myers, Forrest, 1941-., 1 (Box 253)
      - Individual Artists., 118 (Box 253)
        - McCartan, Edward, 1879-1947., 13 (Box 253)
        - McIntire, Samuel, 1757-1811., 4 (Box 253)
        - McKenzie, Robert Tait, 1867-., 8 (Box 253)
        - MacMonnies, Frederick, 1863-1937., 10 (Box 254)
        - MacNeil, Hermon A., 1866-1947., 5 (Box 254)
        - Maldarelli, Oronzio, 1892-., 3 (Box 254)
        - Man Ray, 1921-1963., 10 (Box 254)
        - Manship, Paul, 1885-1966., 36 (Box 254)
        - Marisol, 1930-., 14 (Box 255)
          Also known as Marisol Escobar.
        - Meadmore, Clement, 1929-., 3 (Box 255)
        - Meiere, Hildreth, XX C., 3 (Box 255)
        - Metcalf, Jack, 1925-., 4 (Box 255)
        - Miller, Alec, XX C., 2 (Box 255)
        - Miller, Joseph Maxwell, XIX-XX C., 3 (Box 255)
    - N, 63 (Box 256)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 9 (Box 256)
        - Nagare, Masayuki, 1923-., 3 (Box 256)
        - Nauman, Bruce, 1941-., 4 (Box 256)
        - Newman, Barnett, 1905-1970., 1 (Box 256)
        - Niehaus, Charles H., 1855-1935., 1 (Box 256)
      - Individual Artists., 54 (Box 256)
        - Nadelman, Elie, 1885-1946., 12 (Box 256)
        - Nakian, Reuben, 1897-1986., 2 (Box 256)
        - Nevelson, Louise, 1899-1988., 18 (Box 256)
        - Noguchi, Isamu, 1904-1988., 22 (Box 256)
    - O, 39 (Box 257)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 3 (Box 257)
        - Ossorio, Alfonso, 1916-., 2 (Box 257)
        - Outerbridge, Donald, 1923-., 1 (Box 257)
      - Individual Artists., 36 (Box 257)
        - O'Connor, Andrew, 1874-1941., 6 (Box 257)
        - Oldenburg, Claes, 1929-., 25 (Box 257)
        - Oppenheim, Dennis, 1939-., 5 (Box 257)
    - P, 70 (Box 258)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 19 (Box 258)
        - Packard, Emmy Lou, XX C., 1 (Box 258)
        - Paley, Albert, 1944-., 2 (Box 258)
        - Pan, Marta, 1923-., 1 (Box 258)
        - Partridge, Ordway, 1861-1930., 1 (Box 258)
        - Pattison, Abbott, XX C., 1 (Box 258)
        - Pavia, Phillip, 1912-., 1 (Box 258)
        - Pepper, Beverly, 1924-., 4 (Box 258)
        - Pereira, Irene Rice, 1907-1971., 1 (Box 258)
        - Perkins, Marion, XX C., 1 (Box 258)
        - Peskin, Roger, XX C., 1 (Box 258)
        - Phillips, Helen, XX C., 1 (Box 258)
        - Presiden, E. N., XIX C.?, 1 (Box 258)
        - Price, Kenneth, 1935-., 2 (Box 258)
        - Proctor, Phemister, XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 258)
      - Individual Artists., 51 (Box 258)
        - Paik, Nam June, 1932-., 8 (Box 258)
        - Palmer, Erastus Dow, 1817-1904., 7 (Box 258)
        - Piccirilli, Attilio, 1866-, and Furio, 1870-., 4 (Box 258)
        - Powers, Hiram, 1805-1873., 12 (Box 258)
        - Pratt, Bela Lyon, 1867-1917., 20 (Box 258)
    - Q, 4 (Box 258)
      - Individual Artists., 4 (Box 258)
        - Quinn, Edmond, 1868-1929., 4 (Box 258)
    - R, 135 (Box 259)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 14 (Box 259)
        - Reder, Bernard, 1897-1963., 2 (Box 259)
        - Rendon, Enrique, XX C., 1 (Box 259)
        - Reynal, Jeanne, 1903-., 2 (Box 259)
        - Roberts, Howard, XIX C., 1 (Box 259)
        - Rocklin, Raymond, XX C., 1 (Box 259)
        - Rosati, James, 1912-., 1 (Box 259)
        - Rosenbauer, Wallace, 1900-., 1 (Box 259)
        - Rubins, David K., XX C., 1 (Box 259)
        - Runtze, E. T., XIX C., 1 (Box 259)
        - Russell, Charles Marion, 1864-1926., 3 (Box 259)
      - Individual Artists., 121 (Box 259)
        - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1925-., 6 (Box 259)
        - Reimann, William, 1935-., 3 (Box 259)
        - Remington, Frederic, 1861-1909., 8 (Box 259)
        - Rickey, George, 1907-., 5 (Box 259)
        - Rimmer, William, 1816-1879., 10 (Box 259)
        - Rinehart, William H., 1825-1874., 19 (Box 259)
        - Rivera, Jose de, 1904-., 8 (Box 259)
        - Robus, Hugo, 1885-1964., 7 (Box 260)
        - Rogers, John, 1829-1904., 16 (Box 260)
        - Rogers, Randolph, 1825-1892., 4 (Box 260)
        - Rosati, James, 1912-., 13 (Box 260)
        - Roszak, Theodore J., 1907-., 8 (Box 260)
        - Rox, Henry, 1900-., 3 (Box 260)
        - Rush, William, 1756-1833., 11 (Box 260)
    - S, 209 (Box 261)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 39 (Box 261)
        - Sandback, Frederick, 1943-., 3 (Box 261)
        - Sanford, E. F. Jr., XX C., 1 (Box 261)
        - Sardeau, Helene, 1899-1968., 1 (Box 261)
        - Scanga, Italo, 1932-., 1 (Box 261)
        - Scarpitta, Salvatore Cartaino, 1887-., 2 (Box 261)
        - Schatz, Zahara, XX C., 1 (Box 261)
        - Scheler, Armin Alfred, 1901-., 1 (Box 261)
        - Schlegell, David von, 1920-., 1 (Box 261)
        - Schnabel, Day, 1905-., 1 (Box 261)
        - Schnier, Jacques, 1898-., 1 (Box 261)
        - Sears, Philip S., XIX-XX C.?, 2 (Box 261)
        - Seaver, Elizabeth, XX C., 1 (Box 261)
        - Seley, Jason, 1919-., 1 (Box 261)
        - Sievers, F. William, 1872-., 1 (Box 261)
        - Skillin, Simeon or workshop, c.1800., 3 (Box 261)
        - Slobodkin, Louis, 1903-., 1 (Box 261)
        - Snowden, George H., XX C., 1 (Box 261)
        - Spaventa, George, 1918-., 4 (Box 261)
        - Spero, Nancy, 1926-., 1 (Box 261)
        - Stackpole, Ralph, 1885-., 1 (Box 261)
        - Steiner, Michael, 1945-., 2 (Box 261)
        - Stella, Frank, 1936-., 2 (Box 261)
        - Stone, Sylvia, 1928-., 2 (Box 261)
        - Storrs, John, 1885-., 3 (Box 261)
        - Swarz, Sahl, 1912-., 1 (Box 261)
      - Individual Artists., 170 (Box 261)
        - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus, 1848-1907., 25 (Box 261)
        - Saint-Phalle, Niki de, 1930-., 8 (Box 261)
        - Samaras, Lucas, 1936-., 5 (Box 262)
        - Sargent, John Singer, 1856-1925., 3 (Box 262)
        - Scaravaglione, Concetta, 1900-, 4 (Box 262)
        - Segal, George, 1924-., 17 (Box 262)
        - Serra, Richard, 1939-., 11 (Box 262)
        - Shrady, Henry Merwin, 1871-1922., 4 (Box 262)
        - Smith, David, 1906-1945., 44 (Box 262)
        - Smith, Tony, 1912-1981., 5 (Box 262)
        - Smithson, Robert, 1938-1973., 5 (Box 263)
        - Sonnier, Keith, 1941-., 4 (Box 263)
        - Stankiewicz, Richard, 1922-1983., 7 (Box 263)
        - Steinback, Heim, 1941-., 5 (Box 263)
        - Sterne, Maurice, 1878-1957., 5 (Box 263)
        - Stewart, Albert, 1900-., 3 (Box 263)
        - Story, William Wetmore, 1819-1895., 4 (Box 263)
        - Strider, Marjorie, 1934-., 6 (Box 263)
        - Sugarman, George, 1912-., 5 (Box 263)
    - T, 25 (Box 263)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 8 (Box 263)
        - Tajiri, Shinkichi, 1923-., 1 (Box 263)
        - Todd, Michael, 1935-., 1 (Box 263)
        - Townley, Hugh, 1923-., 1 (Box 263)
        - Turini, G., -1881., 1 (Box 263)
        - Turrell, James, 1943-., 4 (Box 263)
      - Individual Artists., 17 (Box 263)
        - Taft, Lorado, 1860-1936., 5 (Box 263)
        - Talbot, William, 1918-1980., 2 (Box 263)
        - Trova, Ernest, 1927-., 10 (Box 263)
    - U, 3 (Box 264)
      - Individual Artists., 3 (Box 264)
        - Umlauf, Charles, 1911-., 3 (Box 264)
    - V, 14 (Box 264)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 6 (Box 264)
        - Vaillancourt, Armand, XX C., 1 (Box 264)
        - Viviano, Emmanuel G., 1907-., 1 (Box 264)
        - Volk, Leonard W., 1828-1895., 1 (Box 264)
        - Voulkos, Peter, 1924-., 2 (Box 264)
        - Vuchinich, Vuk, 1901-., 1 (Box 264)
      - Individual Artists., 8 (Box 264)
        - Vonnoh, Bessie Potter, 1872-1955., 1 (Box 264)
        - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula, 1942-., 7 (Box 264)
    - W, 42 (Box 264)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 16 (Box 264)
        Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings, a folder devoted to Warren Wheelock, and a folder devoted to Wheeler Williams.
        - Walsh, Bernard, XX C., 1 (Box 264)
        - Warner, Olin L., 1844-1896., 2 (Box 264)
        - Waugh, Sidney Biehler, 1904-., 1 (Box 264)
        - Werner, Nat, XX C., 1 (Box 264)
        - Wesselman, Tom, 1931-., 1 (Box 264)
        - Westerland, Mia, 1942-., 1 (Box 264)
        - Westermann, H. C., 1922-., 1 (Box 264)
        - Wheelock, Warren, XX C., 1 (Box 264)
          See also folder of clippings at beginning of section.
        - White, Lawrence Grant, XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 264)
        - Whitehurst, Byron Lee, 1952-., 1 (Box 264)
        - Wiley, William, 1937-., 1 (Box 264)
        - Williams, Wheeler, 1897-., 1 (Box 264)
        - Wilson, Charles H., 1937-., 1 (Box 264)
        - Wilson, Henry, XIX-XX C., 1 (Box 264)
        - Winslow, George, XX C., 1 (Box 264)
      - Individual Artists., 26 (Box 264)
        - Walton, Marion, 1899-., 4 (Box 264)
        - Ward, John Quincy Adams, 1832-1917., 7 (Box 264)
        - Warneke, Heinz, 1895-., 4 (Box 264)
        - Weinberg, Elbert, 1928-., 7 (Box 264)
        - Weinman, Adolph A., 1870-1952., 3 (Box 264)
        - Whitney, Gertrude Vanderbilt, 1876-1942., 1 (Box 264)
    - X, Y, Z, 41 (Box 265)
      - Miscellaneous Artists., 7 (Box 265)
        - Yellin, Samuel, 1885-1940., 1 (Box 265)
        - Youngerman, Jack, 1926-., 1 (Box 265)
        - Yourievitch, Serge, active 1909-1923., 3 (Box 265)
        - Zeidenbergs, Olaf, 1936-., 1 (Box 265)
        - Zogbaum, Wilfred, 1915-., 1 (Box 265)
      - Individual Artists., 34 (Box 265)
        - Zorach, William, 1887-1967., 34 (Box 265)